Lloyd: Hi, and welcome to the
short video which will explain the
purpose of the Time to Think boxes.
So now that you've started your course,
you will be on page one of session one,
and I would strongly suggest that you
familiarise yourself with the icons
on the page, which will appear at
different points throughout the course.
And they relate to certain things such
as Key Points, Stretches and the Time to
Thinks, Case Studies, Watch and Reads.
And then you have the video which
will explain submitting assessments.
If you have any difficulty with this,
if you just Vmail your tutor and
they will explain how to go about
submitting your assessments correctly.
And then you have the Time to Think
video, which is what you're watching now.
And once you've done that, if you
go to page 2, this then brings you
to your Learning Goals page and it
will give you all of the learning
goals and you can download the
actual full criteria for this unit.
And then a little bit of an introduction,
all about goal setting and creating a
motivation map, and then the hints and
tips, which I would strongly suggest
downloading because they will assist
you when you come to do your assessment.
And then page 3, you are starting the
first page of the course materials.
So as you work through each of the pages
and each of the sessions for each unit
we will watch the videos, the video
transcripts are there, there are quizzes.
There's another video there.
And then you'll come
to the Time to Thinks.
So what you can do with these
is in the Time to Thinks you can
access these from your journal.
So whatever you type
in here will be saved.
And then in your journal, you
will be able to access that.
And I strongly suggest that you
do complete these Time to Thinks.
So quite a lot of them are linked
to the assessment questions, so the
more information that you put into
your Time to Thinks, the easier
it will be when you come to do
your actual assessment questions.
And as I said, there's two
Time to Thinks on that page.
All you would do...
type something in there, click save,
and then that will go to your journal.
And then on the My Course page, so
if I just go back to the top, go
to the My Course page and as you
can see, I have my journal here.
So if I click on the journal,
you'll be able to see that, my note
there -- "hello" -- it was in there.
So for every day, every time you enter
a journal entry, It will be showing
up in the little calendar there.
So you can then navigate through them.
As I say it, I would strongly urge you
to complete them because they will assist
you when you complete the assessment.